泰利 我知道我在这工作时间不长
Terry, I know I haven't worked here very long
不过我在想可否
but I was wondering, do you think it would be possible
预支我一百元的薪水?
if I got a $100 advance on my salary?
预支?
An advance?
这样我才能跟家人一起过感恩节
It's so that I can spend Thanksgiving with my family.
我们每年都会去维尔滑雪场
See, every year, we go skiing in Vail,
一般都是我爸给我买机票
and normally my father pays for my ticket
但是我已经开始独立生活
but I've sort of started this whole independent thing, you know
而这也是我来这里工作的原因
which is actually why I took this job.
瑞秋 瑞秋 亲爱的
Rachel, Rachel, sweetheart.
你是个很糟 很糟 的服务生
You're a terrible, terrible waitress.
真的 真的很糟糕
Really, really awful.
我知道你的意思了 我同意
Okay, I hear what you're saying. I'm with you.
额
Urn...
可是我真的很努力 而且我觉得自己已经进步了
But I'm trying really hard, and I think I'm doing better.
真的
I really do.
有人需要咖啡吗?
Does anybody need coffee?
有 这儿      我要
Yeah over here.        Woman Yeah I do.
你看
Heh. Look at that.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第01季 第09集
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：悠悠慕雪
超狗飞了
The One Where Underdog Gets Away
打扰一下先生 嗨 您是这里的老主顾了
Excuse me, sir? Hi. You come in here all the time.
额 我在想
Uhhuh. I was just wondering
你是否能考虑预支点小费给我?
you think there's a possibility you could give me an advance on my tips?
不
Huh? No.
好 好 没关系的 抱歉以前把咖啡泼到您了
Okay, okay. That's fine, fine. Sorry about that spill before.
只剩九十八块五毛钱了!
Only 98.50 to go.
嗨      嗨
Hey.        Hey.
罗斯 你知道爸妈要去波多黎各过感恩节吗?
Ross, did you know that Mom and Dad are going to Puerto Rico for Thanksgiving?
什么?不 不会的
What? No, they're not.
是的 布莱曼家邀请了他们      你搞错了
Yes, they are. The Blymans invited them.        You're wrong.
我没错      你搞错了
I am not wrong.        You're wrong.
不 我才跟他们聊过
No, I just talked to them.
我要给妈打电话
I'm calling Mom.
嗨 嗨      嗨
Hey, hey         Hey.
嗨      咖啡
Hey.        Coffee.
这是紧急求助部 你化妆了?
And this from the Cry for Help Department: Are you wearing makeup?
是的
Yes, I am.
今天 我的正式身份是乔伊崔比亚尼 演员兼模特
As of today, I am officially Joey Tribbiani, actor/model.
谢谢
Thank you.
真有趣 我刚还想你看起来更像
That's funny, I was thinking you look
乔伊崔比亚尼 男人兼女人
more like Joey Tribbiani man/woman.
你给什么当模特儿?
What were you modeling for?
你们知道免费诊所的海报么?
You know those posters for the City Free Clinic?
哇 那你不就是健康一族的一员了吗
Oh. wow. You're gonna be one of those healthy, healthy, healthy guy.
那个哮喘病人还真可爱
The asthma guy's really cute.
对啊      可不是吗?
Oh, he is.        Isn't he?
知道你会是代言什么么?      不知道
You know which one you're gonna be?        No, no.
不过我听说脑膜炎还缺人 所以...
But I hear Lyme disease is open, so, you know...
祝你好运 希望你能得到
Good luck, man. I hope you get it.
谢了
Thanks.
你说对了 他们怎么可以这样?
Well, you were right. How can they do this to us, huh?
这可是感恩节!
It's Thanksgiving.
这样好了 我在我那儿做晚餐怎样?
Aw. Tell you what. How about if I cook dinner at my place?
我会弄得跟妈妈的味儿一样
I'll make it just like Mom's.
你会做切成块的土豆泥么?
Will you make the mashed potatoes with the lumps?
你知道土豆那样弄其实不对
You know they're not actually supposed to?
我切土豆块
I'll work on the lumps.
乔伊 你要回家 对吧?      对
Joey, you're going home, right?        Yeah.
钱德 你还在抵制所有清教徒的节日么?
And I assume Chandler, you're still boycotting all the Pilgrim holidays?
是的 每一个都不放过
Yes, every single one of them.
菲比 你要跟你奶奶一起过?
Phoebe, you're gonna be with your grandma?
对 还有她男朋友
Yeah, and her boyfriend.
不过我们在十二月过感恩节 因为他过农历
But we're celebrating Thanksgiving in December because he's lunar.
这么说你星期四有空了?
So you're free Thursday, then?
对 哦 我也可以去吗?      当然
Yeah. Oh. can I come?        Yeah.
瑞秋 你还是要去维尔滑雪么?
Rach, you still thinking you're gonna make it to Vail?
当然 咻 咻 咻
Absolutely. Shoop, shoop, shoop.
只是还差102块钱
Only $102 to go.
不是只剩98.5么?
I thought it was 98.50.
对 嗯 是的 不过我打破了一个杯子
Yeah. well, it was, but I broke a cup.
嗯 我要去卡萝家了
Well I'm off to Carol's.
我们为何不邀请她来?
Ooh, ooh, why don't we invite her?
因为她是我前妻
Ooh, ooh, because she's my exwife
她可能想带上她的 哦 哦 同性恋伴侣 一起来
and will probably wanna bring her, och, och, lesbian life partner.
嗨 卡萝在吗?
Hi. Is Carol here?
不在 她去开教工会了
No, she's at a faculty meeting.
我就是过来拿我的头骨
Well, I just came by to pick up my skull.
不是我的 是
Well, not mine, but...
请进      谢谢
Come in.        Thanks.
卡萝借走上课用 我现在得拿回去还给博物馆
Yeah, Carol borrowed it for a class, and I have to get it back to the museum.
长什么样子?
What's it look like?
就像一张没有皮的大脸
Kind of like a big face without skin.
哦 我有印象
Yes, heh, I'm familiar with the concept.
我们可以找找看      好
We can just look for it.        Okay.
哇 你们有很多怎么做女同性恋的书
Wow, you guys, heh, sure have a lot of books about being a lesbian.
嗯 你必须去上课
Well, you know, you have to take a course.
不然他们就不让你当同性恋
Otherwise they don't let you do it.
嘿 乌龟耶尔特 经典故事
Hey, hey, Yertle the Turtle. A classic.
其实我正在念给宝宝听
Actually, I'm reading it to the baby.
还没出生的宝宝?
The baby that hasn't been born yet?
你是不是
Uh, wouldn't that mean you're
疯了?
crazy?
你觉得宝宝在里面听不到声音么?
What, you don't think they can hear sounds in there?
你不是认真的吧? 你真的跟宝宝说话?
You're not serious. I mean, you really talk to it?
对 常常 我想让宝宝认得我的声音
Yeah, all the time. I want the baby to know my voice.
那你 你提到过我吗?
Do you, uh? Do you talk about me?
有 常提      真的?
Yeah, yeah. All the time.        Really?
不过 我们都称你为捐精子的泡泡
But, urn, we just refer to you as "Bobo the sperm guy".
如果她对宝宝说话 我想我也要有一点肚子时间
Look, if she's talking to it, I just think I should get some belly time too.
但我不是说我相信这个
I mean not that I believe any of this.
我信 我想宝宝可以听到所有的声音
Oh I believe it. I think the baby can totally hear everything.
真的?      我可以演示给你看
Really?        I can show you.
也许有点怪异
This will seem a little weird.
你得把头放到火鸡里面
But you put your head inside this turkey
然后我们大家都说话 你就可以听到我们说的
and then we'll all talk, and you'll hear everything we say.
我想说我完全支持这个实验
I'd just like to say I'm totally behind this experiment.
事实上 我很愿意给你的脑袋抹上黄油
In fact I'd very much like to butter your head.
嗨      瑞秋
Hey.       Hey, Rach.
你搞定钱了吗?      没 差远了
Did you make your money?        No, not even close.
忘了维尔 忘了家庭团聚
Forget Vail. Forget seeing my family.
忘了咻 咻 咻
Forget shoop, shoop, shoop.
额 瑞秋
Uh, Rach
你的信
Here's your mail.
谢谢 你放在桌上就好了
Thanks. You can just put it on the table.
嘿 不
Heh. No.
这是你的信!
Here's your mail.
谢了 放在桌上就好了!
Thanks. You can just put it on the table.
你能不能现在就打开!
Would you just open it?
哦 我的天!
Oh, my God.
你们太好了!
Oh, you guys are great.
我们一起凑的
We all chipped in.
我们一起?      你欠我二十块
We did?        You owe me 20 bucks.
谢谢 谢谢大家
Thank you. Thank you so much.
钱德 你的传统节日大餐准备好了
Chandler, here you go. Got your traditional holiday feast.
蕃茄汤
Got your tomato soup
香烤起司配菜 还有特大号的洋葱圈
your grilledcheese fixings, and your familysize bag of Funyuns.
等等 这是你的感恩节晚餐?
Wait, this is what you're having for Thanksgiving dinner?
你跟这个节日到底有什么仇?
What is it with you and this holiday?
好吧 我九岁的时候
All right, I'm 9 years old.
我讨厌这个故事!
Aw, I hate this story.
我们刚吃完一顿丰盛的感恩节大餐
We've just finished this magnificent Thanksgiving dinner
我嘴里 我记得的非常清楚 还塞满南瓜派
I have, and I remember this part vividly, a mouthful of pumpkin pie.
我父母就选择那个时刻告诉我 他们要离婚了
And this is the moment my parents choose to tell me they're getting divorced.
哦 我的天!
Oh, my God.
一旦你有这样的负面印象
It's very difficult to enjoy Thanksgiving dinner
就很难去享受感恩节大餐了
once you've seen it in reverse.
嗨
Hi.
我们一起工作过      有吗?
We used to work together.        We did?
对 在梅西百货的时候 你就是迷幻香水女孩 对吧?
Yeah, at Macy's. You're the Obsession girl, right?
是的      我就是"阿米许"香水的那个
Yes.        I was the Aramis guy.
阿米许?阿米许?阿米许?      哦!
Aramis? Aramis? Aramis?         Oh.
对 是你!
Yeah, right.
我跟你说 你是这行里最棒的
I gotta tell you, you're the best in the business.
别开玩笑了      我说真的
Get out.        I'm serious.
你太厉害了!你就懂什么时候喷 什么时候要往后退
You're amazing. You know when to spritz. You know when to lay back.
真的?我受宠若惊了
Really? You don't know what that means to me.
你今晚闻起来真香 你身上的是什么?
Mm, mm. You smell great tonight. Uh, what are you wearing?
什么也没有
Nothing.
听着 你要不要去喝一杯?
Listen, do you wanna go get a drink or something?
好的...
Yeah. that would be
怎么了?      突然想到我还有事
What's wrong?        I just remembered I have to do something.
什么事?
Oh. What?
离开
Leave.
等等 等等
Whoa. Wait, wait, wait.
马里奥没有告诉你的事
What Mario isn't telling you
性病 你永远不知道谁会染上它
VD: you never know who might have it
我猜你们全都看到了
So I guess you all saw it.
什么?      看到什么?
What?        Saw what?
不 我们只是在笑 你知道 笑是会传染的
No, we're just laughing. You know how laughter can be infectious.
嗨
Hey.
只好另找个地方过感恩节了
Set another place for Thanksgiving.
全家人都以为我得了性病
My entire family thinks I have VD.
今夜的特别节目
Tonight, on a very special Blossom.
看起来不错 好!
Mm, looking good. Okay.
苹果汁在滚 火鸡在烤 山芋香喷喷
Cider's mulling, turkey's turking, yams are yamming.
干嘛?
What?
不知道
I don't know.
就是和妈妈在厨房的感觉不太一样
It's just not the same without Mom in the kitchen.
够了 出去 别来烦我!
Ugh. All right, thats it. Get out of my way and stop annoying me.
哦 这就有点像了
Well, that's closer. That's...
我买到机票了!我买到机票了!
I got the ticket, I got the ticket.
再过五小时 就可以咻 咻 咻
Five hours from now, shoop, shoop, shoop.
哦 你不能再咻了
Oh, you must stop shooping.
好 我要去收拾行李了
Okay, I'm gonna get my stuff.
钱德 你要进来吗?
Chandler, will you just come in, already?
不 我宁愿和欢乐保持安全距离
No, thank you. I prefer to keep a safe distance from all this merriment.
小心!南瓜派来了!
Look out. Incoming pumpkin pie.
你以前来这一套的时候我们都笑了
Okay, we all laughed when you did it with the stuffing,
但这会儿不好笑了
but that's not funny anymore.
摩妮卡 我有个问题 我没看到土豆泥
Hey, Monica, I got a question. I don't see any Tater Tots.
这不叫问题
That's not a question.
但我妈总是会做这个 就像是个传统
But my mom always makes them. It's like a tradition.
叉子上有块火鸡肉 配点蓝莓酱 还有土豆泥!
You get a little piece of turkey on your fork, a little cranberry sauce, and a Tot.
我的意思是 不能和家人团聚已经太惨了
I mean, it's bad enough I can't be with my family
因为我的病
because of my disease.
好吧
All right, fine.
今晚的土豆有切成块的
Tonight's potatoes will be both mashed with lumps
还有做成泥的
and in the form of Tots.
哦耶
Yes.
好了 我要去跟我还没出生的宝宝说话去了
All right, I'm off to talk to my unborn child.
好      妈妈从不打人
Ah.        Okay, Mom never hit.
好了 全部搞定
Okay, all done.
菲比 你在搅烂土豆么?
What? Phoebe, did you whip the potato?
罗斯要吃切块的
Ross needs lumps.
哦 很抱歉 我只是
Oh I'm sorry. Oh, I just I
我还以为我们要弄成泥 然后再放一些豌豆和洋葱
thought we could have them whipped and then add some peas and onions.
为什么要那样做?
Why would we do that?
就像我妈妈曾经做的一样
Then they'd be just like my mom used to make it
你知道 在她去世前
you know, before she died.
好吧 三种土豆吃法出现了
Okay, three kinds of potatoes coming up.
大家再见
Okay. Goodbye, you guys.
谢谢大家
Thanks for everything.
哦 天 你们看 对不起,很抱歉
Oh. God. look at Sorry. I'm so sorry.
最不可思议的事件发生了 超狗飞了
The most unbelievable thing has happened. Underdog has gotten away.
那个气球?      不 是真的卡通超狗
The balloon?        No, no, the actual cartoon character.
当然是气球!
Of course the balloon.
新闻全都在报导 在它抵达梅西百货之前
It's all over the news. Right before he reached Macy's...
它断线了 后来在华盛顿广场公园上被发现了
he broke free and was spotted flying over Washington Square Park.
我要到屋顶上去看 谁要跟我去?
I'm going to the roof. Who's with me?
我不行 我得走了
Well, I can't. I gotta go.
拜托 一只八十英尺的充气狗在城市上面游荡?
Come on, an 80 foot inflatable dog loose over the city?
这样的机会有几次?      几乎没有
How often does that happen?        Almost never.
钥匙拿了吗?      好
Got the keys?        Okay.
随时可以开始
Any time you're ready.
好
Okay.
好 开始了
Okay, here we go.
好 我要对着哪里说? 我的意思是
Okay, where am I talking to here? I mean, uh...
似乎只有那样才能让他听见 但是
Well there is one way that seems to offer a certain acoustical advantage, but
对着隆起的部位就可以了
Just aim for the bump.
好
Okay.
好 好
Okay, okay.
好 开始
Okay, here goes.
你知道吗? 我做不到
You know, I, You know, I can't do this.
这太诡异了 我觉得跟傻子一样
This is, It's too weird. I feel stupid.
没关系 那就别做
All right, so don't do it. It's fine.
不用因为苏珊这么做你就非得也要做
You don't have to do it just because Susan does it.
哈罗 宝宝 哈罗 哈罗
Hello, baby. Hello, hello.
我们眼看超狗的影子坠向公园的那种感觉
that moment when we first saw the giant dog shadow fall over the park?
他们干嘛非得把它打下来? 真的很残酷
But did they have to shoot him down? I mean that was just mean.
现在火鸡应该是外焦
Okay, right about now the turkey should be crispy on the outside.
里嫩了
and juicy on the inside.
我们还站在这儿干什么?
Why are we standing here?
我们在等你开门 你有钥匙
We're waiting for you to open the door. You've got the keys.
不 我没有
No. I don't.
有 你有 我们要出门时 你说 "钥匙拿了"
Yes, you do. When we left, you said, "Got the keys."
不 我没有 我是问 "钥匙拿了吗?"
No I didn't. I asked, "Got the keys?"
不 不 不 你是说 "钥匙拿了"
No, no, no. You said, "Got the keys."
你们谁有钥匙吗?
Either of you have the keys?
烤炉还开着      我得拿机票
The oven is on.        Oh, I've gotta get my ticket.
等一下 我们有你们的备用钥匙
Wait. We have a copy of your key.
快去拿啊!快去!
Well, then get it, get it!
嘿 那种口气不会让我更快一点
Hey, hey. That tone won't make me go any faster.
乔伊      这倒可以
Joey.        That one will.
大家都对我说
And everyone's telling me
"你得选个专业 你得选个专业"
"You gotta pick a major. You gotta pick a major."
所以我鼓起勇气 选了古生物学
So on a dare, I picked paleontology.
你根本不知道我在说什么
And you have no idea what I'm saying,
因为 面对现实吧 你只是一个胎儿
because, let's face it, you're a fetus.
你会很开心你再没有腮了
You're just happy you don't have gills anymore.
你不用一直对他说话 你可以唱歌
Look, you don't have to talk to it. You can sing to it.
拜托 我才不要对着你的胃唱歌
Oh, please. I am not singing to your stomach, okay?
还顺利吗?      嘘 嘘 嘘
How's it going?        Shh. shh. shh.
我们开始了
Here we come
沿着街道走着
Walkin' down the street
每个人的脸上都很开心
Get the funniest looks from Everyone we meet
嘿 你感觉到了吗?      是的
Hey, uh, did you just feel that?        I did.
一直都这样?      不 这是第一次
Well, does it always, uh        No, no, that was the first.
继续唱 继续唱
Keep singing. Keep singing. Oh.
嘿 嘿 你是我的宝宝
Hey, hey, you're my baby.
我等不及要见到你
And I can't wait to meet you.
等你出来了 我要给你买百吉饼 然后一起去动物园
When you come out I'll buy you a bagel. And then we'll go to the zoo.
这次我有感觉到
I felt it that time.
嘿 嘿 我是你的爸爸
Hey, hey, I'm your daddy.
我是那个没有胸部的那个
I'm the one without any breasts.
不是那个      你们可以再快一点吗?
Nope, not that one.        Can you go any faster with that?
嘿 只有一个钥匙孔我却有一大堆钥匙
Hey, I got one keyhole and about a zillion keys.
你自己试试
You do the math.
你们怎么会有这么多钥匙?
Why do you guys have so many keys in there anyway?
以备不时之需 就像现在
For an emergency just like this.
听着 你这嘻皮笑脸的
All right, listen, smirky.
要不是因为你的愚蠢的气球
If it wasn't for you and your stupid balloon
我早就在飞机上对着空姐这样指手画脚了
would be on a plane, watching a woman do this right now.
可是我没有
But I'm not.
我发誓你说你拿了钥匙
I swear you said you had the keys.
不 除非我拿了钥匙否则不会说我有
No, I didn't. I wouldn't say I had the keys unless I had the keys.
显然我没有拿钥匙
And I obviously did not have the keys.
够了 不要再说钥匙了 谁都不准说钥匙
Okay, all right, that's it. Enough with the keys. No one say "keys".
为什么要我拿钥匙?
Why would I have the keys?
因为你说你有
Aside from the fact that you said you did?
但是我没说      你应该有
But I didn't.        Well, you should have.
为什么?为什么?      因为
Why?        Because
为什么? 因为一切都是我的责任吗?
Why? Because everything is my responsibility?
我都做感恩节晚餐了还不够么?
Isn't it enough that I'm making Thanksgiving dinner for everyone?
每个人都要不一样的土豆
Everyone wants a different kind of potato,
所以我就做了各种各样的土豆
so I'm making different kinds of potatoes.
可是有谁在乎我想要哪种土豆?
You know, does anybody care what kind of potatoes I want?
没有 没有 没有
No. no. no!
菲比要豌豆和洋葱的
You know, just as long as Phoebe gets her peas and onions
马里奥先生要土豆泥
and Mario gets his Tots.
这是我的第一个感恩节晚餐 我
It's my first Thanksgiving, and I...It's
全都焦了 我没能
all burnt, and I can't
好了摩妮卡 现在只有狗听懂你的话 所以
Okay, Monica only dogs can hear you now, so
看 门开了 我们进去吧
Look, the door's open. Here we go.
天呐
Oh. God.
哦      哦
Ooh.        Oh.
哦 火鸡烤焦了!
Well, the turkey's burnt.
土豆毁了 土豆毁了 土豆毁了
Potatoes are ruined. Potatoes are ruined. Potatoes are ruined.
我们沿着...
Here we come
沿着街道走
Walkin' down the
这味儿可不像妈妈的厨房
This doesn't smell like Mom's.
是不像 对吧? 你要有土豆块 罗斯?
No. it doesn't, does it? But you wanted lumps, Ross?
给你 这就是你的土豆块
Well, here you go, buddy. You got one.
天 这下可好
Oh, God, this is great.
飞机走了 我想我只能留下了跟你们一起了
The plane is gone, so I guess I'm stuck here with you guys.
嘿 我们都有好的计划 现在这样不是任何人的首选
Hey, we all had better plans, okay? This was nobody's first choice.
哦 真的吗?
Oh, really?
那我为嘛忙得要死
So why was I busting my ass
想弄出一顿美味的感恩节大餐?
to make this delicious Thanksgiving dinner?!
这叫美味吗?      给我闭嘴!
You call that delicious?        You be quiet!
别吵了 别吵了 别吵了!
All right, stop it, stop it, stop it!
这才像感恩节的气氛
Now, this feels like Thanksgiving.
额      怎么了?
Ew.        What?
丑陋裸男 把他的火鸡从烤箱里拿出来了
Ugly Naked Guys taking his turkey out of the oven.
额
Eh.
哦 天呐 他不是一个人
Oh, my God. He's not alone.
丑陋的裸男
Ugly Naked Guy
跟丑陋的裸女 共享感恩节大餐
is having Thanksgiving dinner with Ugly Naked Gal.
我得瞧瞧
I gotta see this.
哇
Aw
丑陋的裸男 好家伙
All right, Ugly Naked Guy.
裸舞开场了
Ooh, ugly naked dancing.
他有伴真的很好
It's nice that he has someone.
我可以开始切了吗?
Shall I carve?
当然
By all means.
好
All right.
谁要浅色起司 谁要深色起司?
Oka who wants light cheese and who wants dark cheese?
我根本不想知道深色起司
I don't even wanna know about the dark cheese.
有人要分吃这块吗?      我要
Does anybody wanna split this with me?        Ooh. I will.
你们得许愿才行
Mm. You guys have to make a wish.
许愿?      得了 你们是知道的 感恩节啊
Make a wish?        Come on, you know, Thanksgiving.
你抢到大块的 你刚才许什么愿?
Ooh. You got the bigger half. What did you wish for?
要比较大块的
The bigger half.
好 我想举杯庆祝
All right, I'd like to propose a toast.
举杯了 叮叮叮
A little toast here. Ding, ding, ding. Mm.
我知道这也许不是你们大家计划的感恩节
This isn't exactly the kind of Thanksgiving you planned
可是对我来说 今天的感恩节真的很棒 知道么
but for me this has been really great, you know?
我想这是因为今天没有离婚
I think because it didn't involve divorce
也没有人呕吐
or projectile vomiting.
我在想 如果你去维尔滑雪
I was just thinking, if you'd gone to Vail
或你去跟家人相聚 或要不是你得
or if you guys had been with your family, or if you didn't have
梅毒或什么的
syphilis and stuff
我们就不可能聚在一起
we wouldn't be all together, you know?
我想我真正想说的是
So I guess what I'm trying to say
谢天谢地你们的感恩节计划全砸了
is that I'm very thankful that all of your Thanksgivings sucked.
太感人了
That's so sweet.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗯
Mm.
也预祝有个糟糕的圣诞节
And hey, here's to a lousy Christmas.
以及更糟的新年
And a crappy New Year
干杯      干杯
Hear.        Hear.
小便失禁?
Bladder Control Problem
停止家庭暴力
Stop Wife Beating
痔疮?
hemorrhoids?
三次东尼奖得主
Winner of 3 Tony Awards
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧